<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><block tag="html">blog.org from David Brake, UK-based Internet
journalist,consultant and virtual community builder
body    {background:#666666; font-family: Verdana, Arial, sans-serif;color: black;}
.blogtitle  {font-family: Verdana, Arial, sans-serif;color: white;font-size:32px;margin-left:20px;margin-bottom:1px; text-transform:uppercase;}
.links  {font-family: Verdana, Arial, sans-serif;font-size:11px;}
A.links:hover{color:white;}
A   {font-weight:bold;text-decoration:none;}
A:hover {color:red;}
.date   {font-family: Verdana, Arial, sans-serif;color: black;font-size:16px;font-weight:bold;margin:10px;}
.posts  {font-family: Verdana, Arial, sans-serif;color: black;font-size:12px;margin:10px;}
.byline {font-family: Verdana, Arial, sans-serif;color: #999999;font-size:11px;}

 body {
  background-color: #666666;
 }
 :link { color: #336699 }
 :visited { color: #003366 }
 :active { color: red }
 p.c3 {text-align: center}
 div.c2 {text-align: center}
 div.c1 {font-weight: bold}
<block tag="body"><block tag="div"><block tag="table"><block tag="tr"><block tag="td"><block tag="div">blog.org</block></block></block><block tag="tr"><block tag="td"><block tag="div">News, comment &amp; net.oddness from <link href="http://davidbrake.org">David Brake</link>, a UK-based
consultant, journalist and virtual community builder.<block tag="p">To contact <link href="http://davidbrake.org/">me</link> or give
feedback on anything you see here, go to my <link href="http://www.worldcrossing.com/WebX?13@42.x6uLa1s7r9M^3@.ee97de5">
message forum</link> or my <link href="http://www.davidbrake.org/contact.htm">contact page</link>.</block><block tag="p"> To be emailed whenever this
weblog is updated, <link href="http://www.spyonit.com/AddPageChangedSpy?location=http://blog.org&amp;title=David+Brake%27s+Blog+has+changed...&amp;description=">
click here</link> and register with Spyonit</block>If checked each link you
follow will open a new browser window<link href="http://www.blog.org/">HOME</link><block tag="div"><link href="http://blogspace.com/rss/feeds/blogify?url=http://blog.org/index.ht ml"> </link><link href="http://logicerror.com/blogifyYourPage">Powered By
Syndicate Your Page</link></block>

Archives:<link href="http://www.blogger.com/"></link></block></block><block tag="td"><block tag="div">Saturday, September 15, 2001</block><block tag="div">The US <link href="http://www.linkcounter.com/go.php?linkid=177427">got what it
deserved</link> say Jerry Falwell and Pat Robertson. Falwell said,
""The abortionists have got to bear some burden for this because
God will not be mocked... I really believe that the pagans, and the
abortionists, and the feminists, and the gays and the lesbians who
are actively trying to make that an alternative lifestyle, the
ACLU, People for the American Way -- all of them who have tried to
secularize America -- I point the finger in their face and say,
'You helped this happen.'"<block tag="p">Enough said...posted by David Brake at <link href="archives/2001_09_09_blogorg_archive.html%235707906">21:45</link></block></block><block tag="div">It seems to be obligatory to post up something
about Tuesday's appalling events. I try to apply a utilitarian
approach to problems, however emotive they may be. As a result, I
am apprehensive when I hear talk about a "war" on terrorism and
particularly early press speculation about a possible invasion of
Afghanistan (or possibly a punitive expedition?). Paul Wolfowitz,
deputy Pentagon chief, is quoted as saying the US would "end states
which sponsor terrorism." The terrorist attacks themselves were bad
enough, but there is a danger that:<block tag="p">1) they may encourage further bigotry among Americans against
Muslims and/or arabs, most of whom are not at all sympathetic to
the aims of the terrorists. In the Telegraph here in the UK <link href="http://www.linkcounter.com/go.php?linkid=177191">Daniel
Pipes</link> suggests 10-15% of Muslims are "Islamists" (his term for
militants) and says we must worry about Islamist "sleepers" (or in
other words any Muslim even if they *seem* peaceable).</block><block tag="p">2) they may cause huge disruption to people's lives in a futile
attempt to make the world "safe". I don't think it is actually
possible to secure the world against determined terrorists without
an unacceptable level of inconvenience and paranoia. <link href="http://www.linkcounter.com/go.php?linkid=177192">John
Keegan</link>, Defence Editor of the Telegraph has already suggested
that ISPs should be required to forbid the transmission of
encrypted messages (!) and uncompliant providers on foreign
territory should expect their buildings to be destroyed by cruise
missiles (!!!)</block><block tag="p">3) they may cause the US to lash out blindly against people they
see as enemies - if they attack Afghanistan or other nations which
house terrorists they will likely cause large civilian casualties
and huge resentment in the Muslim world, breeding many more
terrorists to take their place.</block><block tag="p">4) they may set back the middle east peace process for years to
come. Simplifying grossly, Israel is the intransigent party these
days and Bush was already closely aligned with Israel. Now there is
a danger that some Palestinians' anger at the US for historical
reasons will be exploited by opponents of their cause to make a
just settlement look like surrender to terrorism.</block><block tag="p">If the terrorists and their leaders can be found and killed or
captured, of course I would like to see that happen (and I wouldn't
be too fussy about the methods used as long as they weren't
indiscriminate like cruise missiles) but I think it would be both
wrong and dangerous to make this into a larger war or crusade. The
terrorists don't represent anyone but themselves - if we launch a
jihad against a whole culture then they will have achieved their
goal.</block><block tag="p">Frankly, I believe that even this lacklustre President would not
be foolish enough to ignite such a conflagration (and if he were, I
doubt his advisors would let him) but I still worry that the
inflammatory suggestions like the ones we are starting to see in
the press are deeply un-helpful.</block><block tag="p">To comment on this or other aspects of the attack on America,
visit my <link href="http://www.worldcrossing.com/WebX?14@26.vbRDbd6BVu5^309706@.eee018e">
discussion forum</link>.posted by David Brake at <link href="archives/2001_09_09_blogorg_archive.html%235693877">00:26</link></block></block><block tag="div">Thursday, September 13, 2001</block><block tag="div">Apologies for a slow update - I am at the <link href="http://www.cira.org.uk/creativeandconnected/">Creative and
Connected</link> in Middlesbrough (NE England). I may share more
thoughts on the US bombings later but for now I would just like to
mention that the European Union has announced a three minute
silence at noon on Friday to express solidarity with the terrorism
victims.posted by David Brake at <link href="archives/2001_09_09_blogorg_archive.html%235660973">13:46</link></block><block tag="div">Tuesday, September 11, 2001</block><block tag="div">Goodbye and good riddance to the poisonous Jesse
Helms. Here is a collection of some of his <link href="http://atlanta.creativeloafing.com/news_feature2.html">words
and wisdom</link>.
Found via <link href="http://www.fark.com/">Fark.com</link>posted by David Brake at <link href="archives/2001_09_09_blogorg_archive.html%235610196">13:23</link></block><block tag="div">Monday, September 10, 2001</block><block tag="div"><link href="http://www.linkcounter.com/go.php?linkid=175621">Euro MPs
plan ban on spam</link> - It looks like there may be a U turn from the
bone-headed position championed by a Labour MEP, Michael Cashman.
Earlier this year an EU committee backed a proposal to allow
companies to send emails to customers unless the customers opted
out of receiving them. Fortunately, a majority of MEPs voted to
force companies to wait for an "opt in" and sent the proposed bill
back to committee.posted by David Brake at <link href="archives/2001_09_09_blogorg_archive.html%235586895">11:12</link></block><block tag="div">Clever Web Tricks (cont.) - how to put a mailto:
link to your email address without letting spammers get at it.
Visit <link href="http://www.linkcounter.com/go.php?linkid=175611">
this page</link>, which converts your email address text into text
that browsers will understand but "spiders" which try to capture
email addresses will not. My mailto using this technique comes out
as
"mailto:%64%61%76%69%64%40%64%61%76%69%64%62%72%61%6b%65%2e%6f%72%67"
but works as normal: <link href="mailto:%64%61%76%69%64%40%64%61%76%69%64%62%72%61%6b%65%2e%6f%72%67">
david@davidbrake.org</link>. If this doesn't work with your browser or
you see another problem with it, please let me know!posted by David Brake at <link href="archives/2001_09_09_blogorg_archive.html%235586373">10:08</link></block><block tag="div">Friday, September 07, 2001</block><block tag="div"><link href="http://www.linkcounter.com/go.php?linkid=174450">Toxic Sludge
is Good For You</link> An interview with the author of the
aforementioned book about the PR industry in the US. There is no
question that there are lots of horror stories to be found when you
spend your life looking at how corporate spin runs America, but I
think he over-states his case when he says,<block tag="p">"Corporations really are all about money, and anything else
really is public relations and image building."</block><block tag="p">For more of the same see PR Watch<link href="http://www.linkcounter.com/go.php?linkid=174451"></link>.posted by David Brake at <link href="archives/2001_09_02_blogorg_archive.html%235537564">12:28</link></block></block><block tag="div">Wednesday, September 05, 2001</block><block tag="div"><link href="http://www.linkcounter.com/go.php?linkid=173871">The Hunger
Site</link> is back under new ownership. Please tell everyone you know
- From a high in December 2000 of 405 tonnes of food, donations are
down to less than 100 tonnes for the coming month at this rate
(presumably because everyone thinks they are still gone). Found via
<link href="http://gelwan.com/followme.html">Follow Me
Here</link>posted by David Brake at <link href="archives/2001_09_02_blogorg_archive.html%235495325">14:19</link></block><block tag="div">The FT argues that the <link href="http://www.linkcounter.com/go.php?linkid=173870">Telecomms
bubble</link> is a bigger deal than the dotcom bubble. This figure
surprised me - "nearly half of European bank lending in 1999 was to
telecoms companies." And Dan Roberts, the writer, estimates that a
trillion dollars of the telecoms investment during the bubble was
wasted...<block tag="p">And yet even with all of this investment in telecoms we still
don't all have the access to inexpensive broadband that would help
to save what is left of the dotcom industry.posted by David Brake at <link href="archives/2001_09_02_blogorg_archive.html%235494789">13:15</link></block></block><block tag="div">Monday, September 03, 2001</block><block tag="div">Making accountants sound cool? I wouldn't mind
being called a <link href="http://www.linkcounter.com/go.php?linkid=173321">
cognitor</link>...posted by David Brake at <link href="archives/2001_09_02_blogorg_archive.html%235453980">14:43</link></block><block tag="div"><link href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/hi/english/sci/tech/newsid_1502000/1502820.stm">
Delhi children make play of the net</link> - It turns out that for all
of our complaints that computers are too complicated, even
illiterate street children will eventually figure out how to
download MP3s if you leave a computer around...posted by David Brake at <link href="archives/2001_09_02_blogorg_archive.html%235453795">14:27</link></block><block tag="div"><link href="http://www.technologyreview.com/magazine/sep01/mannall.asp">
Technology Review - Taming the Web</link> A thought-provoking piece
which shows the weaknesses in arguments made by 'old skool'
Internet libertarians claiming the net is impossible to
control.
For example - distributed apps tend to be inefficient unless they
have some central servers (which can be targeted) and off-shore
companies can still have their servers and assets in more regulated
companies targeted (because small nations tend to have poor
Internet access).
The author also says that hacking works for general computing but
codes can be made secure in special-purpose hardware. This argument
is weak as DVD player and camcorder hacking shows...posted by David Brake at <link href="archives/2001_09_02_blogorg_archive.html%235453361">13:48</link></block><block tag="div"><link href="http://www.well.com/user/derb/blog/">HOME</link></block></block></block></block></block><block tag="p"><link href="http://rd1.hitbox.com/rd?acct=WQ500129KAAW57EN0"></link></block></block></block>
