<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><block lc="24" awpl="2.1" alwl="5.6" rnlt="6.16">
            .topNav {



              background-color: #ff8040;background-image: url(/images/topnavi_yellow2.jpg);



          
            }
            .topNav2 {
        background-image: url(/images/topnavi_tree2.jpg);
            }

    
 Calaba - Press Releases <block lc="24" awpl="2.1" alwl="5.6" rnlt="5.62"><block lc="17" awpl="1.9" alwl="5.5" rnlt="8.3"><block lc="9" awpl="2.6" alwl="4.7" rnlt="13.88"><link href="/">Home</link> &gt;  <link href="/news/">News</link> &gt;  Calaba Press Releases <block lc="7" awpl="3" alwl="4.7" rnlt="15.08">Press Releases <block lc="1" awpl="3" alwl="4" rnlt="11.17">London  -  <link href="240701.html">24 July 2001</link> - Calaba Limited, the leading provider of wireless data discovery tools, is pleased to announce its membership in the Openwave Developer Alliance Program. </block><block lc="1" awpl="3" alwl="3.7" rnlt="19.82">London  -  <link href="060601.html">6 June 2001</link> - Calaba Limited, a leader in the mobile internet industry, publishes  Top of the WAPs  its ranking of the top WAP subjects and top 20 WAP sites based on usage trends on Wapaw, Calaba's leading WAP-based search engine and directory service for the mobile Internet. </block><block lc="1" awpl="3" alwl="3.7" rnlt="40.45">London  -  <link href="310501.html">31 May 2001</link> - Calaba Ltd and Speedy Tomato UK today announced that Calaba's searchable mobile Internet directory, Wapaw, is available on Speedy Tomato UK's multi-access mobile Internet portal, wap.speedytomato.co.uk. The Wapaw wireless directory offers users access to a growing directory of more than 3,500 sites of wireless content, as well as the unique ability to customise the directory of WAP sites according to an individual's chosen language, location, interests and content type, offering customers relevant info with minimal effort. </block><block lc="1" awpl="3" alwl="5.3" rnlt="14.38">Cannes  -  <link href="210201.html">21 February 2001</link> - Calaba is announces the world's first wireless Deep Link Directory, a new technology which empowers its Wapaw wireless directory to catalogue not just top-level WAP sites but deep into specific pages offering users more relevant information on wireless data devices. </block><block lc="1" awpl="3" alwl="5.3" rnlt="10.06">London  -  <link href="201100.html">20 November 2000</link> - Calaba Ltd, provider of the most advanced search engine and directory for the wireless Web, announced the appointment of leading UK Internet pioneer Valerie Holt as Company Chairperson. </block><block lc="1" awpl="3" alwl="5" rnlt="9">London  -  <link href="011100.html">1 November 2000</link> - Calaba Ltd, a fast-growing wireless Internet start-up, announced the completion of a Euro 1.5 million round of financing from ADD Partners and Delta Partners. </block><block lc="1" awpl="3" alwl="3.7" rnlt="12.91">London  -  <link href="240500.html">24 May 2000</link> - Calaba, an Internet startup specialising in wireless search technologies, announced the launch of Wapaw, their WAP search engine and directory affiliate program. </block></block></block></block></block></block>